これまでの実験の結果からして
Ｄメールは 過去に
送られていることが実証された
うん でも フェイリスたんとの
勝負の結果は 改変できなかったお
それは お前自身の問題だ
The experiments we've run so far
まっ ルカ子の件も含め
精度には問題があるが
prove that the D-mails are being sent to the past.
改良すれば 本物のﾀｲﾑﾏｼﾝが完成…
ﾀｲﾑﾏｼﾝ？
But I couldn't change the outcome
of my match with Feyris-tan!
おっ な… 盗み聞きか？
That's a problem with you, not with the D-mail.
フェイリスは
ご注文をお持ちしただけにゃん
There are problems with the system,
ｶﾞﾑｼﾛとﾐﾙｸは 入れますかにゃん？
断る！
including the issue with Rukako,
but if we work on it,
we can turn it into a real time machine...
そんな凶真には
全部 入れちゃうにゃん
Time machine?
うん？
You were listening to us?
にゃんにゃん
出た－！
Feyris just brought your order!
秘技 ｢目を見て混ぜ混ぜ｣
羨ましす オカリン
Do you want any gum syrup or milk?
凶真 タイムマシンって
何のことかにゃん？
I refuse!
And thus, you can have my everything!
そんな色仕掛けで 機密事項を
漏らすとでも？
There it is!
う… 凶真には聞かないにゃん
ダルにゃ～ん？
Secret Move: Stir While Gazing Into Their Eyes!
I'm so jealous, Okarin. Explode.
フン ダルが 俺を裏切るとでも？
過去にﾒｰﾙを送れるﾏｼﾝを作ったお
Kyouma, what do you mean by a time machine?
主に 僕が…
秒殺にも程がある！
Do you think you can seduce me
into giving up classified information?
過去に… メールを？
I won't ask Kyouma.
Daru-nyan!
You think Daru would betray me?
We built a machine that sends texts to the past!
And by "we," I mean mostly me!
That was entirely too fast!
Messages to the past?
Chaos Theory Homeostasis
ダルのヤツ
部外者に 秘密事項を漏らすと…
Stupid Daru...
Spreading our secrets to outsiders...
どうして？
うん？
Why?
どうして そういうふうにとるの？
私は ただ…
Why must you take it that way?
I just wanted to...
違う そんなつもりじゃ！
私は… あっ
No, that isn't what I meant!
I...
うん？
あっ おっ おお…
あっ
ななっ なな… 何だ？
泣いてない
Wh-Wh-What?
I'm not crying!
別に 泣いてなんてないから！
It's not like I was crying, okay?
なっ！ どう見ても 泣いてただろ
You were clearly crying...
まだ 目が赤いぞ
Your eyes are still red.
はっ あ…！
ちっ 違う！ これは 目にゴミが…
No!
Something's in my eye...
お前は 昭和のドラマか
What is this, an old soap opera?
とっ とにかく泣いてない
Anyway, I'm not crying.
だから 追及しないこと
分かった？
So no questions.
Got it?
別に 追及するとは
一言も言ってない
I didn't say anything.
う… うるさい！
Shut up!
え？
おっ おお…
はあ…
うっ うう…
え？
うっ うっ…
うっ…
クリスティーナ…
うっさい 話しかけんな！
Christina...
Don't talk to me!
これだけは 言っておく
I'll only say this...
お前は 大切な仲間だ
You're part of my life now.
相談には いつでも乗る
Any time you want to talk, I'll listen.
岡部…
Okabe...
フハハハハ…
計画どおり
ころりと ワナに はまったぞ
Just as planned, she fell for it!
ああ これで 徹底的に
こき使えるというものだぁ～
Now I can use her for all the grunt work!
フ～ハハハハ…！
おい
Hey.
お疲れさまにゃ～ん
Good work out there!
ああ フェリスちゃん！
これから 凶真のところかにゃん？
Feyris-chan!
Are you heading to Kyouma's?
うん お昼ごはんを買ってきてって
Yeah, he wanted me to bring lunch.
ふ～ん
ねえ まゆしぃは
見たことあるにゃん？ ﾀｲﾑﾏｼﾝ
Hey, have you seen the time machine, Mayushii?
うん？ タイム…
Time...
ああ！ 電話レンジさん？
Oh, Phone Microwave-san?
電話レンジ？
Phone Microwave?
バチバチ～って雷みたいのが
There's this big spooky lightning,
and it's kind of scary...
こう… ビリビリって
ちょっと 怖いんだ～
すっごいにゃん！ 映画に出てくる
タイムマシンみたいにゃん
Wow!
It's like a time machine out of the movies.
うん… でも まゆしぃは
Yeah...
But Mayushii doesn't really want
him doing that stuff.
あんまり ああいうこと
してほしくないんだけどな
どうしてにゃん？
う～ん なんか
Why?
It feels like Okarin is leaving me.
オカリンが 遠くに行っちゃう
感じがするのです
では これより 円卓会議を…
オカリン オカリン
We will now begin our Round—
Okarin! Okarin!
うう… 何だ？
おかしくね？
What?
Isn't this strange?
まゆ氏は 自分では
コスプレしないと言ってたお
Mayushii says she isn't cosplaying.
コスプレではない 学校の制服だ
It isn't cosplay.
It's her school uniform.
今日 登校日だったんだ
I had school today.
学校の制服… う～ん 完成度 激高
It's a super-realistic portrayal of a school uniform.
｢完成度｣とかいうの
普通にセクハラだから
That's sexual harassment,
and she doesn't have to accept it.
はい オカリンの分
Here's yours, Okarin!
ああ… って違う！
円卓会議だと言ってるだろうが！
Thanks.
No, wait. I said we're having a Round Table!
お昼 買ってきてって言ったのは
オカリンだよ？
You're the one who wanted me to bring lunch.
気にしなくていいわよ
どうせ 大した話じゃないんだから
Don't mind him.
Obviously, it isn't anything important.
それは 今日の議題を
聞いてからにしてもらおう
You can say that after you hear
the discussion topic...
ズバリ
｢物理的タイムトラベル｣だ！
Physical time travel!
まゆり 麦茶 冷蔵庫にまだある？
Mayuri, is there still barley tea in the fridge?
ちょっと 待っててね～
One second.
完成度 高…
Realistic.
俺だ！ 機関による ラボ内の
切り崩し工作が始まったようだ
It's me!
The Organization has initiated
an operation to tear apart the lab.
この鳳凰院 凶真の言葉が…
ラボメンの心に届かないのだ！
The words of me, Hououin Kyouma,
fail to reach them!
それ 前からじゃね？
なら なぜ！
Do they ever?
Then why are you ignoring my awesome topic?
このすばらしい議題を
華麗にスルーするのだ！
無理に決まっているからでしょ？
Because it's impossible.
メールは 過去に送られているのだ
We can send messages to the past.
可能性は…
ない！
It must be possible...
It's not.
送れるのは
36バイト プラスアルファ
We can send thirty-six bytes plus some extra.
６文字×３通 それ以上は 無理
Three messages, with six characters.
No more.
試したければ
自分 使って 実験してみれば？
If you want to experiment,
why not be the guinea pig?
ゲルオカリンになっても
よければ…
That's if you don't mind ending up as a gel-Okarin.
ゲルオカリンか～
痛すぎ
Gel-Okarin, huh?
That'd really hurt.
物理的タイムトラベルの難しさは
ＳＥＲＮの実験が証明している
SERN's experiments prove the difficulties
inherent to physical time travel.
世界最大のＬＨＣを使っても
成し遂げていないのよ？
Even using the LHC, biggest in the world,
they've had no success.
こんな設備で できるわけない
We can't possibly do it with this equipment.
なら なぜ
メールは送られている？
Then how do the messages get to the past?
分からない それが問題なの
I don't know.
That's the problem.
前にも言ったように ＳＥＲＮは
ブラックホールとリフターの力で
Like I said before,
SERN's trying to use the
lifter-black hole combination
タイムトラベルを
可能にしようとしている
to achieve time travel.
この電話レンジも
恐らく原理は同じ
The Phone Microwave probably
works on the same principle.
なのに リフターに相当するものは
レンジの中にはない
But the microwave doesn't have anything
to function as a lifter.
どこにある？
さあね
So where is it?
I don't know.
Ｄメールが送れる時間も
まだ限られているし
We're limited in the times
we can send D-mail, too.
現状では まだこれを
Currently, we can't be sure that this machine
過去にメールが送れるマシンとは
言えないわ
really sends messages to the past.
先に進む前に
今あるものの解明が先よ
Before we continue,
we should deal with the issues before us first.
つまらん！
Boring!
科学なんて
99％は つまらないものの積み重ね
99.9% of science is boring.
あんたも科学者を自称するなら…
科学者ではない！
If you call yourself a scientist...
I'm not a scientist!
マッドサイエンティストだと
言っているだろうが！
I'm a mad scientist!
駄目だ こいつ
早くなんとかしないと…
Yo, I heard you like fail, so we put some fail in your fail,
so you can facepalm while you facepalm.
うん？
牧瀬氏？
Miss Makise...
あっ
貴様 まさか…
You aren't a...
うっ うるさい それ以上 言うな！
そんなわけないから！
Shut up!
Not another word!
Because that's impossible!
はっ 早く 話を進めなさいよ
Get back on topic, already.
では 続いて 報告に移る
Continuing on to the reports.
ＳＥＲＮｻｰﾊﾞｰ内にあった ﾃﾞｰﾀの
翻訳状況はどうなっている？
How's the translation of
the SERN server documents going, Christina?
クリスティーナ…
もとい ねらーよ！
AKA, 2channer!
だから 違うって言ってんだろ！
の割には ＩＤ真っ赤に…
I told you that's not true!
Then you sure know your memes.
してない！ うっ うう…
I do not!
とっ 特に 報告することはないわ
Nothing to report.
そうか 引き続き 調査を頼む…
I see.
Continue your investigations...
ねらーよ！
｢ねらー｣って言うな！
2channer!
Stop calling me that!
次にダル ハッキングの状況は？
Daru's up next. How's the hacking coming?
変わりない 別サーバーにある
No change.
Probably, until I analyze the mysterious program
謎のプログラムを解析しないと
状況は 変わらないと思われ
on the other server, there'll be no change.
IBN5100での解析は？
How's the IBN 5100 analysis going?
それができれば
言うことなしなんだな
Be great if I could do it.
ど… どういうことだ？
｢どういうこと｣？
What do you mean?
Huh?
まだ
解析をしていないということか？
You haven't started the analysis?
あ？ どうやってやるん？
あっ！
How should I do that?
IBN5100は どこにある？
Where's the IBN 5100?
僕が知るわけないっしょ！
How would I know?
まさか…
It can't be...
あっ！
オカリン どうしたの？
Okarin, what's wrong?
クリスティーナ…
Christina...
もしかして 俺は
IBN5100を 見つけていないのか？
Did I, by any chance, not find the IBN 5100?
もしかしても何も
You don't even know where it is.
どこにあるかも
分かってないじゃない
なるほどね
仮に その話を信じるとしたら
I see.
So if I decide to believe what you say,
you found the IBN 5100.
岡部は IBN5100を見つけた
ああ… お前と一緒に
ここまで運んできた
Yes.
I carried it back here with you.
けど その記憶は
岡部以外の 誰にも残っていない
But you're the only one with any memory of that.
恐らく
Ｄメールによる 過去改変ね
The D-mails probably changed the past.
なっ… 過去改変？
Changed the past...
But we've only sent minor stuff.
しかし 送った内容は
ささいなものばかりだぞ
バタフライ効果よ
The Butterfly Effect.
過去に１つのメールを送ることで
そこから 世界線は分岐する
Sending one message into the past
causes the world line to split.
ロト６を買わなかった世界から
買った世界へ
From a world where we didn't buy a Lotto-6 ticket
to one where we did.
それによって
あったはずの出来事や
Little by little, this changes what
was meant to happen.
事実が少しずつ変わっていく
１つの変化は
玉突きのように 次の変化を起こし
One change causes another,
and they pile on top of one another.
それは 次第に大きくなっていく
昔からよく言われている
過去改変のリスクの一つよ
It's one of the long-recognized risks
of altering the past.
では IBN5100は どこに？
Then where is the IBN 5100?
逆に聞く どこにあったの？
Let me ask this instead.
Where was it?
あっ！
Yes, when I asked my dad,
he said it used to be here, but...
はい… ええ お父さんに聞いたら
確かに
奉納されているというのですが…
今は どこにも…
It's gone now.
そうか
I see.
どうだった？
Well?
確かに
柳林神社に IBN5100はあった
There was an IBN 5100 at Yanabayashi Shrine.
が 現在はない
But it's gone now.
誰がいつ 持ち出したのかも
分からない
No one knows when it was taken or by whom.
行き止まりか…
A dead end, huh?
でも 神社にパソコンを
奉納するなんて 不思議だね
But it's strange to donate a PC to a shrine.
I wonder who'd have done that.
誰が そんなことしたんだろう？
あっ！
ふう…
フェイリスちゃん
にゃんにゃん？
Feyris-chan?
What's up?
今度のイベントの
メイドさんへの自由な質問
Here's the list I wrote of ten questions
これにしようと思うんだけど…
ど～れ どれ～？
to ask the maids, at the next event.
Let me see...
｢過去に戻って
一つだけやり直せるとしたら
"If you could go back and redo one thing
from your past, what would it be?"
何をしますか？｣
フェイリスちゃんは 何する？
えっ…
What would you do, Feyris-chan?
そうだにゃあ…
Let me think...
フェイリスは…
Feyris... doesn't look back at her past! Let's go.
過去は 振り返らないにゃ！
前を向いて歩いていくのが
It's the task of the cat-eared maid,
みんなに幸せを届ける
猫耳メイドの使命にゃん！
who brings everyone happiness, to forge ahead!
あっ
ああっ！
あっ 電話… 電話っと
Oh, my phone!
はい フェイリスにゃん…
あっ 凶真
Hi, this is Feyris.
Kyouma.
にゃっ パソコン？
A PC?
IBN5100だ
An IBN 5100.
柳林神社に
奉納したという事実は あるか？
Did your family give it to Yanabayashi Shrine?
にゃ～
う～ん よく覚えてにゃいけど
I don't really remember...
パパが 古いパソコンを
But you're right. My dad did have a lot of old PCs.
たくさん持っていたのは
確かにゃん
凶真…
Kyouma...
それは さっき言ってた｢ﾀｲﾑﾏｼﾝ｣と
何か 関係があるにゃん？
Is this related to the time machine
you were talking about?
うわあ 見て見て！
Look, look!
うーぱ… メタルうーぱだよ！
It's an Upa!
A metal Upa!
やはり
メタルうーぱが欲しいのか？
Do you still want a metal Upa?
｢やはり｣？
Still?
何分 ここにいるつもりだ？
もう 行くぞ
How long are you going to
stand there, staring at it?
あっ 待ってよ～ ダルく～ん
Wait!
Daru-kun!
お待たせしますた
Here I am!
うん？ なっ！
ああ… 何を買ってるんだ？
What are you buying?
いやあ
瞬殺だった限定版 見つけたん
I found a limited-edition that had
sold out before I could buy it!
オカリン風に言うと
You might say,
｢この巡り会い
まさに 運命石の扉の選択｣
"This encounter was the choice of Steins Gate!"
軽々しく使うな！
Don't use it for stuff like this!
大体 お前たち
なぜ ついてくるのだ
Anyway, why are you two following me?
You could've stayed back at the lab,
with the assistant.
助手と一緒に
留守番していればいいだろ
フェイリスたんの自宅と聞いたら
凸せざるを得ないだろ 常考
Once I heard you were going to Feyris-tan's place,
I had to come along!
まゆしぃだって 遊び行きたいよ～
I wanted to go and play, too!
フェイリスのヤツ
どうして 自宅に来いなどと…
Why did Feyris tell me to come to her house?
あ～！ キラリちゃんだ～
It's Kirari-chan!
Mayuri, wait...
ああっ まゆり おい！
まったく…
Jeez...
The IBN 5100.
IBN5100…
あっ！
Shining Finger!
閃光の指圧師！
待て おい！
Wait! Hey!
あっ！
ちっ！
Shining...
シャイニング…
萌郁！ 桐生萌郁！
Moeka!
Kiryuu Moeka!
くっ！ あっ…
はあっ はあっ はあっ はあっ…
あっ ああ！
Why?
どうして…
ＦＢは あるって言ってたのに…
FB said it was there!
あっ 岡部 君…
Okabe-kun...
Back there, you mentioned the IBN 5100...
さっき IBN5100と…
うっ…！
知ってるの？ どこにあるのか…
Do you know where it is?
You don't know, either?
お前も 知らないのか？
I don't...
知ら… ないの？
But you're right. My dad did have a lot of old PCs.
オカリ～ン
Okarin!
あっ 萌郁さん？
ああ…
Moeka-san?
Yeah.
Okabe...
Moeka-san's so pretty and stylish.
萌郁さん
きれいで スタイル抜群だな～
コスプレしたら
きっと 映えそうだよ
I'm sure she'd make a great cosplayer.
ああ…
あっ まゆり お前
Mayuri, you know Shining Finger?
閃光の指圧師のことを
知っているのか？
え？ 知ってるよ？
I do!
How?
なぜだ なぜ知ってる!?
How do you know her?
オカリンが～ 連れてきたよ～
You brought her to the lab!
なっ！
After Moeka sent her D-mail,
萌郁が Ｄメールを送ったあと
萌郁の存在は
みんなの記憶から消えた
she disappeared from everyone's memory.
And then, after Ruka sent his D-mail,
そして
るかがＤメールを送ったあとには
再び 萌郁を
知っている状態になっていた
they knew her again.
メールによる過去改変が
起きる度に
Little by little, the world changes,
each time the D-mail changes the past?
事実が
少しずつ 変化しているのか？
本当に ここなのか？
Is this really the place?
間違いないよ
I'm sure of it.
えっと～ 一番上みたい
Seems it's on the top floor.
お嬢様は もう間もなく参ります
The mistress will be here soon.
Just one moment.
お待ちください
Butler cafés aren't my thing.
僕 執事喫茶の方は
ちょっと趣味じゃないのだが
本物だよ～ 初めて見た～！
A real butler!
I've never seen one before.
フ～ハッハッハッハ…！
見ろ 人がゴミのようだ！
Look!
The people all look like ants!
いい眺めだ！
フ～ッハッハッハ…！
I love it!
Okarin...
オカリン…
言うと思った…
Thought he'd say that!
Sorry for the wait.
お待たせしたにゃん
あっ フェリスちゃん
Feyris-chan!
うお～
今度は フェイリスたんの私服！
Now it's Feyris-tan wearing her normal clothes!
What luck!
なんたる僥倖 はあ はあ はあ
Feyris Nyan Nyan!
フェイリスにゃんにゃん！
にゃん？
It seems I must question your true identity!
どうやら お前の正体を
聞いておかねばならないようだな
Feyris is...
フェイリスは…
...Feyris-nyan!
フェイリスにゃん！
ふざけるな！
Stop fooling around!
If you refuse to explain, then I'm leaving!
説明がないのなら 帰らせてもらう
Oh, fine.
しかたがないにゃん
フェイリスの家は ここら辺の…
Feyris's family owns all the land around here!
大地主だったんだにゃん！
じゃあ もしかして 秋葉って…
うん そういうことにゃん
Then Akiba is...
That's right.
え？ 秋葉がどしたん？
フェリスちゃんの 本名だよ
What about Akiba now?
It's Feyris's real name.
｢秋葉 留未穂｣ちゃんって
いうんだよ？
Akiha Rumiho-chan!
あ～あ～あ～！ 聞こえない！
I didn't hear that!
フェイリスたんの本名は
フェイリスたん！ う～う～
Feyris-tan's real name is Feyris-tan!
A sad attempt to escape reality.
見苦しい現実逃避だな…
By the way, Feyris was the one
ちなみに 秋葉に萌え文化を
取り入れるようにお願いしたのは
who asked to bring moe culture to Akiba.
フェイリスなのにゃん！
なっ そこまで！
No way!
And she works as an angel at May Queen,
そして 自らも
天使としてメイクイーンで
萌え文化の浸透に
努めているなんて… なんて神！
to further spread moe culture!
How splendid!
そんな神に いち早く注目した
僕の目も神！
And my eyes are also splendid,
for recognizing her before anyone else!
でもでも～ 今の話は
But, but... Keep it a secret, okay?
ないしょにしておいて
ほしいにゃん
I want you to treat me
みんなも 今までどおり
ﾌｪｲﾘｽﾗﾌﾞで 接してほしいにゃん
with Feyris-love, just like always!
I will! Totally!
接します！ 全力で！
ありがとにゃんにゃん
Thank you, nyan-nyan!
にゃんにゃん でもない！
それより IBN5100についてだ
No nyan-nyan!
Anyway, what about the IBN 5100?
ああ そのことにゃん？
Oh, that?
But before that, I have a simple request...
でも～ その前に
簡単な お願いがあるんだけど～
貴様 取引しようというのか！
You want to arrange a trade?
そんなに
難しいことじゃないにゃん
It's nothing difficult.
I only want you to let me
use the D-mail. Just once.
ただ 一度だけ
Ｄﾒｰﾙを 使わせてほしいだけにゃ
なっ！
お安いご用だお！
Sure!
Use it as often as you want!
一度と言わず 何度でも…
待て！
Wait! The D-mail is absolutely
off-limits to outsiders...
Ｄメールは
部外者には 絶対 秘密の…
Then why not make Feyris-chan a lab member, too?
だったら ﾌｪﾘｽちゃんも
ﾗﾎﾞﾒﾝになればいいんじゃないかな
いや 待て 待つのだ！
Wait! Wait!
これ以上 Ｄメールを送るのは…
Sending more messages to the past would be—
私利私欲でロト６当てようとして
メール 出しておいて！
You're the one who sent the
Lotto-6 number back, to try and make money!
And you can't send one for Feyris-tan?
フェイリスたんは ダメだと？
Just once!
一回だけだよ～
いや そういうことではなく…
No, that's not it...
しかし ここでやめたところで
IBN5100が戻ってくる保証はない
But if I stop now,
there's no guarantee that
the IBN 5100 will return.
少しでも
手がかりにつながるなら…
If this becomes any kind of clue...
分かった
ただし まゆりも言ったように
Very well.
But just as Mayuri said,
フェイリスには
ラボメンになってもらう
you'll have to become a lab member.
You are now Lab Member 007, Akiha Ru—
お前は 今日から
ラボメンNo.007 秋葉 留未…
I-I-I can't hear you!
あ～あ～あ～ きっ 聞こえない！
出来たにゃん
It's done.
本当に
送るのは 10年前でいいんだな？
You're sure you want to
send it back ten years, right?
間違いないにゃん
I'm sure!
メールの内容は？
What's does it say?
それは… 秘密だにゃん！
Well... It's a secret!
Tell me.
そういうわけにはいかない
俺には ラボのリーダーとして
As leader of the lab, I have a duty to know.
その内容を知っておく義務が…
ダメにゃん！
No. A maiden's private life is off-limits to guys.
乙女のプライベートは
男子禁制にゃん！
I think it's wrong to look at someone's mail.
ひとのメール見るのは
よくないと思います
激しく同意！
なっ ぐ… しかたないか
I agree! Totally!
Fine.
では 送信ボタンに手を置いて
待て
Then put your hand on the send button and wait.
ハロー
俺だ そちらの状況を伝え…
Hello?
It's me!
What's the situation...
あの女 切りやがった！
そりゃ 切られるっしょ
She hung up on me, damn it!
Yeah, I bet she did.
That Christina!
クリスティーナめ 助手の分際で…
Doesn't she know she's my assistant?
Hello?
ハロー
鳳凰院 凶真だ 無言で切るな
It's Hououin Kyouma.
Don't just disconnect me, without a word.
鳳凰院…？ なんだ 岡部か
いたずら電話かと思った
Hououin? Oh, Okabe.
I thought it was a prank call.
You saw my number on the display.
こちらの番号は
表示されていただろう
それでも
いきなりあんなこと言われたら
Even so, those first words
気味悪くなって 切るわよ
are creepy enough to make me hang up.
フンッ それは つまり
In other words, you are terrified of
the mighty Hououin Kyouma—
この鳳凰院 凶真に
畏怖を覚えているで…
She hung up on me! She hung up on me again!
あいつ また切った
また切ったぞ！
Okarin, aren't you ready yet?
オカリン まだ～？
待て！
Wait!
あの 冷血放蕩天才HENTAI少女め！
Curse you, cold-blooded, pervert girl genius...
Hello?
ハロー
聞け！ ザ･ゾン…
Listen, The Zomb—
ハロー
わ… 私
Hello?
Hello, my name is Okabe Rintarou.
岡部 倫太郎と申しますが
何？
What is it?
電話レンジ(仮)の設定を
I would be extraordinarily gratified
先ほど お送りさせていただいた
おメールのとおりに
if you'd set the Phone Microwave
(name subject to change)
お設定して 置きどおして
いただきたく思うのですが…
to the values I proferred in my earlier message.
最初からそういえばいいのよ
ぐっ…
You should have just said that from the start.
Also, that isn't what "proffer" means.
それと 敬語 変だから
You're embarrassing yourself.
日本人として
それじゃあ 恥ずかしいわよ
あと 電話ﾚﾝｼﾞの(仮)っていうのも
いいかげん…
And stop calling it the Phone Microwave
(name subject to change), already.
だ～！ 黙れ このセレセブが！
下手に出れば いい気になりおっ…
Shut up, Cel-7!
I'm trying to be polite, and you're...
何でもありません
仲が悪いのかにゃ？
Do they not like each other?
I think it's the opposite.
このまま切らずに…
多分 いいんじゃないかな
Agreed.
まゆ氏に 同意
幸い はい で ございます
Will you send?
やっぱり…
うん？
Maybe...
Maybe I don't need to do this.
やっぱり メールは しなくても…
フェイリス！
あっ！
Feyris!
放電が始まった
The electricity's started.
Send it.
送信しろ！
うっ…
うっ ううっ！
あっ… あの…
うん？
Um...
Who are you?
あなたは…
はあ？
えっ…
パパ！
Daddy!
Daddy?
パパ？
Were you talking to Kyouma?
凶真と話していたのかにゅ？
ああ
Yeah.
I'll be on my way.
では 私は これで
どうぞ ごゆっくり
Enjoy yourselves.
フェリスちゃんのお父さんって
なんか 気品があるね
Feyris-chan's dad has this
kind of refined air about him, doesn't he?
Indeed! You can tell he's Feyris-tan's dad.
さすが フェイリスたんの父君を
名乗るだけはある！
Um...
あの！
うん？
Do you know anything about an IBN 5100?
IBN5100を ご存じですか？
随分 懐かしい名前ですね
I haven't heard that name in ages.
I'm looking for one.
捜しているんです
残念ですが…
Unfortunately, I parted with mine a long time ago.
もう 随分 前に
手放してしまいまして…
もしかして
柳林神社に 奉納されたとか…
Did you give it to Yanabayashi Shrine?
Shrine?
神社… いえ そのようなことは…
No, I didn't.
Goodbye, then.
では 失礼
Before Feyris sent her D-mail,
フェイリスが Ｄメールを送る前
I heard that the IBN 5100 disappeared
after it had been given to Yanabayashi Shrine.
IBN5100は
神社に奉納されたあと 消えた
が 今度は
そもそも 奉納されていない
But now, the shrine never got it.
Each time we send a message, things change.
メールを送る度に
何かが少しずつ 変わっていく
Something may be changing,
俺の知らないところでも…
何かが
変わっているのかもしれない
even without my being aware of it.
もしかしたら…
It's possible that we've already
done something that can't be undone.
俺たちは もう 取り返しの
つかないことを…
Okarin! Okarin!
オカリン オカリン
あっ
Mayushii is going to Nakano
to buy an Ai-Sword doujinshi.
まゆしぃは ｢哀ソード｣の
同人誌 買いに
中野に寄るので 帰ります
Ai-Sword?
｢哀ソード｣？ 甲賀ゆいか
Kouga Yui?
Nakano's far away.
中野とは…
随分 遠回りするのだな
Yeah.
うん ｢とらのあな｣
こっちの方にも あればいいのにな
I wish there were a Tora no Ana here.
なっ 何を言っているのだ
What are you talking about?
Tora no Ana's right over there.
｢とらのあな｣なら そこに…
えっ…
What are you talking about, Okarin?
オカリン 何 言ってるの？
Why would there be one in Akiba?
秋葉にあるわけないっしょ
なぜだ？ どうなっている？
アキバから ｢萌え｣が
すべて 消失しまったというのか？
オカリン 待ってよ～
どうしちゃったの？
｢とらのあな｣も ｢アニメイト｣も
どこに いったのだ？
｢まんだらけ｣や ｢ゲーマーズ｣は？
何 言ってるの？ オカリン
そんなの アキバにあるわけないよ